YUVAL KATZENSTEIN NAHMIAS

929-247-5445

Yuval.kanahmias@gmail .com

491 Columbus Avenue Apt 5B New York, NY, 10024

Languages

English-MotherTongue Hebrew-MotherTongue

Additional Certificates

Screenwriting
Certificate, New York
Film Academy

Sailing Instructor, Wingate Institute

Regional Sailing Pilot, Israeli Sailing Association

Grade 30 Boat
Operator, boat operator
in coastal waters,
Shipping and Ships
department, Ministry of
Transport

PROFILE

Experienced in research projects, writing intel reports and briefs. Ability to manage teams and teach high level material both personally and in front of large audiences. Comfortable working independently and as part of a team. Experienced with customer service and training. Highly motivated to learn new skills.

EXPERIENCE

Bookseller, Barnes and Noble — 2023-Present

 Responsible for handling customer transaction, upselling, and offering book suggestions.

System Implementer, Candiru — 2021-2022

- Constructed full on boarding and on going implementation materials of the company's Cyber product for both technical and non-technical international customers.
- Wrote user guides on different features and communicated them to customers.

Techno-Intelligence analysis Course instructor, Unit 8200, Military Intelligence — **2020-2021**

- Designed, built, and taught a 16-week professional intelligence course.
- Edited and corrected my trainee's intel reports, making sure to send detailed update reports of their progress to the relevant managers.
- · Managed the logistics of my trainees.

Techno-Intelligence analysis in English, Unit 8200, Military Intelligence — **2018-2020**

- Was part of techno-intelligence operations that demanded achieving high goals under immense pressure, thinking outside the box quickly and efficiently with great self-assessment.
- Read and processed large amounts of texts in English and deducted relevant conclusions and wrote concise intel reports to be delivered to higher ranking officers.

EDUCATION

Military Command Course, Cyber and Intelligence training center — 2020

High School Diploma, "Ramot Yam" high school, Israel — 2017